Hi, my name is Gavin and I'm here with Bits, our robot dog.
And today we're at the OpenMind headquarters where I'll walk you through our fully autonomous
features powered by OpenMind's BrainPak and the NVIDIA Jetson Thor. We're going to walk through
mapping, loss and found, and auto self-charging features here at the OpenMind headquarters in
San Francisco. So let's get started with onboarding and mapping. When Bits wakes up,
he's going to ask me a series of questions to start the onboarding process.
Hello, I am Bits and what is your name? Hi Bits, my name is Gavin.
Gavin, thank you. You are registered. And just like that, my identity has been registered
and now Bits will start mapping. I'm ready to walk around and map the area.
So this is the OpenMind office and right now Bits has begun roaming around,
tagging different locations like the main floor, office, and living room. So now that Bits has
completed mapping of the entire office floor, we could command him to go to anywhere in the office.
For example, hey Bits, go to the living room. I'm leading you to the living room.
And so now Bits is going to take me to the living room.
So not only will Bits lead me to different locations that it's mapped, but as it's mapping,
it's also tracking different objects. For example, I left my wallet on the sofa,
so now I could ask Bits, hey Bits, I left my wallet somewhere. Can you please find it?
Wallet found on the main room floor on the sofa.
So as we can see here, Bits has found my wallet somewhere and remembers it.
And now he's leading me to the sofa.
And just like that, Bits has found my wallet on the sofa. So it's at the end of the day,
and we could command Bits to go self charge. Bits can you go charge?
I am going to charge now.
So now Bits is going to his self charging station and he's using the QR code to line up with the
charger. So I'm going to charge now. So now Bits is going to his self charging station and he's
So now Bits is going to his self charging station and he's using the QR code to line
up with the charging pad and take his rest. You won't have to worry about manually recharging
your robots. They'll handle it all for you. So this was some of our fully autonomous
features that we've been able to develop here at OpenMind. Using the OpenMind Brain Pack,
as well as the NVIDIA Jetson Thor, we've been able to develop these features in house. But
because we're an open source platform, other developers are able to build their own applications
and features and deploy them on OM1. This is really just the beginning for robot use cases,
and we're excited to bring you more. So follow us and stay tuned for the future.